Do you have any references?
Certificate of aptitude...
Professional experience with a BTS...
Work-study program at the Bayer Institute...
Two hours I'm waiting, go ahead, no, no!
According to the contract, you also have an outbuilding.
Get up, Philippe!
Who is this guy?
Everyone around you is worried.
He is tall, he is strong, he has two arms, two legs, a functioning brain, he is healthy.
It's too long right now!
The guys from the cities, they have no mercy.
That's what I want.
No mercy.
There you go.
Is it good like that?
Wait a minute.
It's a phew thing there.
You're done playing, aren't you?
But in fact you feel nothing at all there.
Enjoy your meal.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
It borders on laziness there, we have to send back a little.
Don't you want to set sail?
You want to get out of here, right?
And where are we going?
Breathe a little.
What is this goal game?
Hey, my gout, it's fucking!
Open your eyes.
What a horror.
No.
Nein.
I will...
Do we agree that here I am your arms and legs?